all right the time still 30-some I make an attempt to to put something on
好的，时间还是30点左右，我试图在上面放一些东西
the website half an hour ago so the lecture from last Tuesday and today's lecture
网站半小时前，所以从上周二开始的讲座和
今天的演讲一定在那里，其余的都可以，我要去的入门者
must be there okay the rest is available starters I'm going to be collecting what
收集我过去的一切还好，我想可能还会再有两个
I had coming okay and I think probably two more on will email those register
通过电子邮件发送给那些注册书籍中一些主题的人以供阅读
some topics from books to read let's see another announcement we're going to post an
让我们看看另一个公告，我们将发布早期作业，但这是
early homework but it's nobody need you for another three weeks or so but I
再过三周，没人需要你，但我想让你知道什么
want you to just know what
is coming and just not reading and in the process of the homework we're going
再过三周，没人需要你，但我想让你知道什么
来了，只是不读书，在做作业的过程中，我们要去
is coming and just not reading and in the process of the homework we're going
明天要朗诵，所以我们可以介绍给你
to have recitation tomorrow so should we can introduce you to yesterday we did move
昨天我们确实将您所做的介绍转移了，这使我进行了一些编程
what you have done introducing led me to some programming aspects cocoa from vista graphical
从可可图形焦点的方面可可，因为我认为唤醒正在准备中
focus because I think the Wake is preparing the homeworks he wants you to start
他要你开始做的小图书馆
building little libraries that eventually lead to large-scale problems now if you don't want us
如果您不希望我们发展这个问题，最终会导致大范围的问题
to develop this libraries in homework 1 we're gonna pass the solutions so you can
作业1中的库，我们将通过解决方案，以便您可以从
use from the second part hours but lastly whatever we post does it means the
第二部分，但最后我们发布的内容都代表我正确的事情
right thing I mean we are also students and we post whatever so hopefully you
意味着我们也是学生，我们发布任何内容，希望您能做得更好
can do better than than us and hopefully there are solutions we post are your
比我们要多，希望我们发布的解决方案是您的解决方案
solutions that's why I want you to factor right up and paste okay and what
这就是为什么我希望您将因子分解并粘贴好
什么是其他公告，所以在此过程中，我们将有一个
was the other announcement and so in this process of we will have a recitation
this Friday but as I told me
什么是其他公告，所以在此过程中，我们将有一个
这个星期五的朗诵会，但是正如我告诉我的那样，讲台的讲课方式相同
very station the same ways the lectures are not thorry so if you don't like
不担心，所以如果你不喜欢见我
to see me you don't have to come you know there are video lectures everything
您不必来就知道有视频讲座一切都在线
is online you can watch me from your kitchen basically we're getting a cup of
你可以从你的厨房看我，基本上我们要喝杯咖啡
coffee but there's gondola station at the same time of driving and again net1 Authority
但是在开车的同时还有缆车站，再次是net1 Authority
because hold information will be posted
因为保全信息将被发布，所以雷克萨斯的功课还可以，所以
and so the homework the Lexus okay so you will notice when you reveal the
您会发现，当您从一张幻灯片中看到幻灯片时，会有一些
slides from let's do one there are some
topics that are not covered okay now those topics are really some little bit more
您会发现，当您从一张幻灯片中看到幻灯片时，会有一些
现在还没有涵盖的主题，这些主题确实有点
examples from the concepts that was
试图交流其中一些概念的更多例子是
trying to communicate some of them are going to come in this lecture so I
将要在本讲座中讲到，所以我不必去做，3D女士会讲到
don't have to do them some lady 3d will cover on Friday some we have
在星期五，我们必须自己阅读一些内容，但是如果有的话
to read them on your own okay and but if there is anything essential I
任何重要的事情，如果我不介绍，我都会回到它的意思上，这意味着我们不
will go back to it okay if I don't cover it means we don't really
need it for the shell code so for
任何重要的事情，如果我不介绍，我都会回到它的意思上，这意味着我们不
外壳代码确实需要它，因此例如有一个大案例研究
example there is a big case study of publicity graphical model related to the biology
与生物学有关的宣传图形模型，你们知道
and as you guys know there is
nobody from biology actually I was asked yesterday polygamy I said we have any students
与生物学有关的宣传图形模型，你们知道
生物学上没有人昨天我被问及一夫多妻制，我说我们有
in biology doing this type of
生物学专业的学生在做这类事情，例如，不要后悔，你知道，所以我
things like not sorry you know so I don't know if I stopped working for
不知道我是否停止了20分钟的生物学工作并且我点击了
20 minutes in biology and I did clicker on the slide maybe a third of
幻灯片可能有三分之一的人接触到了生物学，但这不会
humans reached biology and that is not gonna be  good right  pointing all the way around okay
一路正确指向正确的好
我们将开始讨论有关条件独立关系的限制
we're going to start discussing a limit about conditional independence relations and graphs but the
和图表，但该条件的理论方面的背景
context of theoretical aspects of this conditional independence relations not the graphs represent this is
独立关系而不是图表所代表的这是不纯的
sort of an impure much so we will probably go back to it again and
因此在接下来的23周内，我们可能会一遍又一遍地恢复到原来的状态，因此我们
again for the next 23 weeks so we
have a very reduced understanding so - you can take the concepts today the lecture
因此在接下来的23周内，我们可能会一遍又一遍地恢复到原来的状态，因此我们
因此了解的程度非常有限-您可以今天就采用这些概念
scrolling up you'd be easy but
讲座向上滚动，您会很轻松，但是您知道自己并没有从中受益
you know you don't have from the stir everything ok this is if you have
一切正常，这是如果您的变量绝对显示为零
variables are showing absolutely zero independence relations this is an appreciation of the visionary all
独立关系，这是对有远见的人的赞赏
right so look at it carefully all right not x1 x2 given x1 x2 be
所以仔细看吧，不是x1 x2给定x1 x2  x1像这样几个不同的位置，因为例如我可以开始
given x2 x1 several different positions like that because for example I can start with
x2 and the next one you will
所以仔细看吧，不是x1 x2给定x1 x2  x1像这样几个不同的位置，因为例如我可以开始
如果知道x1和x3，则使用x2和下一个将会体验x3
experience x3 given you know x1 and x3 etc etc so in essence you have
等等等等，所以从本质上讲，您非常推崇那些，并且在某些方面不是
very shove those and in some ways are not symmetric right the way that I
对称，就像我写它们一样，对称球形也可以
write them so same sort of symmetry sphere ok this expansion is very expensive to
进行此扩展非常昂贵，因此，如果我们有您，请对此稍作检查
do so just nibble on this if we have you say K values for its
说出变量X的K值，而您两个都没有，所以这需要一个
variable X and you have both no so this will require a table of the
order of KT power V and
说出变量X的K值，而您两个都没有，所以这需要一个
KT幂V的量表，这就是我们真正开始的原因
this is the reason really we started probabilistic graphical models because we be asking a
概率图形模型，因为我们要问的问题结构可以
question structures can you actually simplify this conditional distributions accountable for some independence relations other
您实际上简化了这种有条件的分配
独立性关系其他了解方式，您也可以探索
ways you know looking at this is well explore given x1 depends on x2 and
给定x1取决于x2和x3告诉x2和x3的趋势，答案是肯定的
x3 telling the trend of x2 and x3 the answer is yes we would factorization
我们将分解效率很高，因此
that is very efficient so the discount that I did here it does not account
我在这里所做的折扣不考虑每个项目的归一化
for normalization of each of these probabilities which is really it doesn't remove much of
这些概率实际上并不能消除很多成本，因此
the cost and so when you want a perfect one you can okay numbers to
当你想要一个完美的人时，你可以用数字来描述它
describe it k square to describe excellent even x1 take you to describe this and
平方来描述甚至x1都可以带您描述这个并采取
take the power bill escape to describe now we'll study machine learning right if you
电力账单逃逸描述一下，现在我们将学习机器学习，如果您有
have missed admission like that and if you want to visit in the context in
那样的错过入场，如果你想在自我的背景下参观
the self classification problems there's a lot of text you can do but you don't
分类问题您可以执行很多文本操作，但不必
have to deal with complexity of K to the me and so here's one example
处理我的K的复杂性，所以这是我要说明的一个例子
I'm going to making tables for each of this conditional probability distributions but inverse you
为每个这种条件概率分布制作表格
但是相反，您可以将它们替换为逻辑回归纵坐标，如下所示：
replace them with logistic regression ordinates looks like  that
好好吃，你在这里看到
alright so delicious that you see here it's so tight and we're from the field
太紧了，我们来自领域本身，这取决于所有
itself in here it depends on all the
previous axis so I try to fit this distribution of science enjoyed a function with
太紧了，我们来自领域本身，这取决于所有
前一个轴，所以我尝试适应这种科学分布，
previous axis so I try to fit this distribution of science enjoyed a function with
与某对手的函数在某种程度上是向量X的两倍
a rival of somewhat it's doubly times the vector X for a for the previous
ones and then we may have not
与某对手的函数在某种程度上是向量X的两倍
以前的那些，然后我们可能没有看到过，但是是的与众不同
seen this but yeah vs. are different there's no no services sigmoid function and the
没有服务的S形函数，标签的焦点取为K
focus of a label to take the K
component of the argument and there is a nice model for this provision from a
没有服务的S形函数，标签的焦点取为K
参数的组成部分，并且从
component of the argument and there is a nice model for this provision from a
他们的电影，你将不必修复
movie of them and you won't have to fix a thing with to describe them
用它们来描述它们的事情现在还可以，但是问题通常是
okay now it's not but the question is normally and I have the calculation here
我在这里进行计算，因此，如果有人有能力利用我的力量
so if anybody has any places from the power I get it it's actually still
得到它实际上仍然比他们想要你做那些事情的几率高
taller than they want you to do the odds of those different against yourself so
与您自己不同，所以它出自此职位，是K
it comes out of the the the post of this is K times miss Claire
几次想念克莱尔，然后才可能知道我的力量
before the possible straight to the power of me you know it's okay to whisper
可以窃窃私语，所以这真的是我的意思，进攻取决于
so it's really I mean depends offensively is but they they significantly reduce from above
他们从上述过程中明显减少了，但是这种方法不是
course okay however this method is not
very useful because each of this conditional distributions depends on the values of all the
他们从上述过程中明显减少了，但是这种方法不是
非常有用，因为每种条件分布都取决于
very useful because each of this conditional distributions depends on the values of all the
所有其他先前变量的值，因此您希望能够
other previous variables so you want to be able to do maths very sort of
数学软件在大学软件中是非常重要的事情，所以如果您
business in the college software plus fire so if you want people mixtures and you
想要人与人之间的混合，并且想要五个模块，这些都可以作为证据
want five modules you know account for evidence and things like that you won't be
而且类似的事情您将无法使用该模块进行代数
able to do the algebra using this module okay but again there is more than
但是，除了这个以外，我们还有其他的桌子，炸得不错，还有一些
this one we have the tables nice fried this had some function alright and in
函数正常，在这种情况下，一旦有了它，这个矩阵就很少了
this case a few this matrix not many once you have it then this could
那么在分类的背景下这可能是一个容易出现的问题
be an easy problem figure in the context of classification so what I want to
所以我想在本课程中做到这一点，我们将不会做一些更好的基本操作
do this in this course we won't do something better some basic  things probability integral syndrome
事物概率积分综合症
有条件独立，所以我有1除以XY和Z可以是标量K
conditional independence so I have 1 divided by XY and Z can be scalar K
vector so I say that x and y are
有条件独立，所以我有1除以XY和Z可以是标量K
向量，所以我说x和y在给定Z 1 FX 2的条件下是独立的
conditionally independent given Z 1 FX 2 the y and z is equal to B
给定C ok，y和z等于B FX，因此tom是Drive的正常现象
FX given C ok so tom is a normal something of Drive make a difference
在x的值上有所不同okay，所以这是一种方法
when it comes to the value of x okay so this is one way to
I'd the traditional dependent of X for y
在x的值上有所不同okay，所以这是一种方法
我将X的传统依存关系y y乘以Z，这很重要，这就是为什么
double Z this important that's why you say conditional because there is an argument either
说有条件的，因为如果您认为现在有一个论点，或者是宇宙论
now cosmas if you think this is a definition let me say the simple algebra
这是一个定义让我说一个简单的代数对，我可以写这个
right I can write this more effectively y and z and then P of Y
y和z更有效，然后Y的P给定Z，所以这些是我可以写的
given Z so those are this I can write
this as P of X given Z P of Y given C so we can
y和z更有效，然后Y的P给定Z，所以这些是我可以写的
这是X的P给定的Y的ZP给定的C，所以我们可以在委员会中推进
advances in the Commission to life as an alternative way that when this conditional distribution
生命作为一种替代方式，当这种有条件的价格分配时
for price is like knob Direction Y an independent commission along Z okay so sometimes
就像旋钮方向Y沿着Z方向独立执行一样，所以有时 候这很方便，因为它们是完全一样的
this will be convenient sometimes this
they are exactly the same thing that's  good
就像旋钮方向Y沿着Z方向独立执行一样，所以有时 候这很方便，因为它们是完全一样的
好的依赖关系也可以用随机变量集来表示，所以我们
okay dependence relationship also in terms of sets of random variables so we can either
可以同意对环境的情感正在发展
assent affection for environments is developing once that wagon easy when texas independent of Y
当得克萨斯州独立于Y时，对集合X中的每个X给出Z时，旅行车很容易
given Z for every X in the set X and
everyone in the sidewalk okay and actually this Zia can make it also set so
当得克萨斯州独立于Y时，对集合X中的每个X给出Z时，旅行车很容易
人行道上的每个人都可以，实际上Zia可以做到
I maybe that we have been even
设置好，所以也许现在我们已经在其中进行了更广泛的逆转
more generalized reversals in there now for example we say this set of the very
例如，我们说这个给定的那个集是非常独立的
most is independent that given that set
variable so this basically will follow  this definition here
例如，我们说这个给定的那个集是非常独立的
变量，因此这基本上将遵循此定义
variable so this basically will follow  this definition here
驱蚊剂我们听这种正交性条件，但是在某些情况下
the repellents we listen to this sort of orthogonality condition but in some probability looks
概率先生。人格状况可能暗示其他事情
mr. personality condition may imply something else usually defined in terms of expectations okay but
通常根据期望定义
for us this is the notation we're
但是对于我们来说，这就是我们将要使用的肌肉独立性的概念
going to use muscle independence basically you know we take this definition for example means
基本上你知道我们以这个定义为例
of perfection y is given p FX he apply okay I was just looking at
完美y赋予p FX他应用了，好吧，我只是在看这张幻灯片
this slide right you can stab it sometimes because you see for example have I'm
您有时可能会刺穿它，因为您看到例如我正在使用
using the notation carrying them in a violent way but hopefully we can still get
符号以暴力的方式携带它们，但希望我们仍然可以
the message for example you know here I lose capital X and wife on the
消息，例如，您知道在这里我损失了资金X，而底部的妻子是
bottom was here in little x and y then effectively the same force but you
在这里x和y很小，那么实际上是相同的力，但是你知道
know traditionally this would be the lot of the volume or this will be the
传统上，这将是大量的交易或这将是价值
values that are the vitamin can take but you know we're okay right we're not
那是维生素可以服用的，但你知道我们没事吧，我们不会
gonna see you know sorry you with a little X you know it's gonna tell
看到你知道，用X表示抱歉，你知道这会告诉你我输入这个
you I type this slide at least we have some slides to talk about the
至少我们有一些幻灯片来谈论您所知道的错误论文
wrong papers you know it's good idea to sort of be careful and consistent because
保持谨慎和一致是个好主意，因为远比您
much than you're consistent okay so this mess intent of this conditional and marginal independence
一贯的好吧，所以这个有条件的和边缘的混乱意图
okay so I am saying here
独立性好，所以我在这里说，这整个时间都独立于
that this whole time is independent of  the type of the car okay
汽车的类型还可以
[音乐]
[Music]
我的意思是，您知道他们说a的可能性更高，您知道我
I mean the you know they say the probability of a is higher is you
know I mean they you know would be exactly the opposite effect from the first
我的意思是，您知道他们说a的可能性更高，您知道我
意味着您知道他们将与第一个示例完全相反
example okay so so this is the motion again so we're gonna verse here you
好吧，所以这又是议案，所以我们要在这里经文，你知道我在
know I'm writing this is a standard are gonna spend actually two or three lectures
写这是一个标准，实际上要花两三堂课
discussing about this kindle market or
讨论这种点燃市场或州立公园庄园州立空间
in the State Park Estate state-space models but this is a Markov chain so we
模型，但这是一个马尔可夫链，所以我们可以想像您知道您有某种状态
can imagine you know you have some state
body moves but and you know the values of it Connie so x1 is the
模型，但这是一个马尔可夫链，所以我们可以想像您知道您有某种状态
身体移动，但是你知道它的价值
body moves but and you know the values of it Connie so x1 is the
康妮，所以x1是重音的音量-谢谢，等等，所以异常
volume of dynomonics - thank you it cetera so the unusually a monomial assumption here
这里的单项式假设中，高BP的模型效应仅取决于
where the model effects of high BP depends only on the value of I'm XT
我的值是XT减去1，所以准备这个表达式可以特别显示出
minus 1 so prepared this expression show expecially we can remember this pretty does this
还记得这个漂亮的长表达式吗？
long expression compared list right with this Markovian model that is very simplified because extra
马尔可夫模型非常简化，因为额外模型不依赖于XT减
doesn't depend on XT minus 2 XT minus 3 etc ok so this is this
2 XT减3等，所以这是他们看到各种提示的时候
moment they see various cues the
independence relations in particular but XP is independent X 2 minus 1 is in the
2 XT减3等，所以这是他们看到各种提示的时候
特别是独立性关系，但是XP中的独立性是X 2减去1
parent of all the various values XT
该课程中所有各种值的父项XT减去2 X 1
minus 2 X 1 on this course or something if I highlighted from lecture 1
如果我在第1课中突出显示了该节点的父节点，那么在此
which is the parent of the node right so in this case if we look
如果我们不给父母做生意的话，那么这是一个基本
at no business to parents okay and so here's a fundamental
公平性有条件地关系了此有向图的先前关系，因此
fairness conditionally previous relations for this directed graph and so what it says x-ray is
它所说的X射线与负片的主要部分无关
independent from the main the segments of a negative spiral so this is out there
螺旋形，所以这是在那里塔玛拉沟槽强调
Tamara trenched to emphasize the depositor given this will highlight in that movie alright so
鉴于此，存款人将在那部电影中突出显示
好吧，这样的说法仍然存在，那就是
the parlance it stays that the value of
V is independent through the name of the sender so photographer at the political order
好吧，这样的说法仍然存在，那就是
V通过发件人的名字是独立的，因此政治上的摄影师
V is independent through the name of the sender so photographer at the political order
命令错误的后代将有数字，但它们基本上是
the wrong descendants will have numbers but they are basically everything about the values of
关于父母价值观的一切基本上都按顺序排列
the parents basically in the order okay these are the non descendants right so point
这些是非后裔，所以要指出父母的价值观
on the values of the parents
excuse you the fella from the non-descendants eye or anything like that right so view
这些是非后裔，所以要指出父母的价值观
请您从非子孙后代或其他类似的事物中解雇您的小伙子
excuse you the fella from the non-descendants eye or anything like that right so view
正确的，所以在这一点上，我只想让您直观地了解一下
at this point I just want you to visualize as to what this means because
we love I think we should
正确的，所以在这一点上，我只想让您直观地了解一下
意味着因为我们爱，我认为我们应该强调那不是很 难，但是一旦有了这一点，就可以定义概率的组成
highlight that which is not very difficult but once you have this the composition for
probability defined on this graph you move rains pushing too hard okay so we will
意味着因为我们爱，我认为我们应该强调那不是很 难，但是一旦有了这一点，就可以定义概率的组成
您移动的这张图下雨太难了，好吧，我们将能够
able to take advantage of this relation so and no Pascal will ensure that only
这样关系的优势，因此Pascal不会确保只有
distillation of the fertilizer in this
该图中的化肥蒸馏满足了这种关系
graph satisfies this relation and around this dilution on the graph this relation is also
这个关系图上的稀释度也满足了，你知道我的意思是你
satisfied you know I mean you
can see sorry  alright so both ways this will be okay
这个关系图上的稀释度也满足了，你知道我的意思是你
可以看到抱歉，所以这两种方式都可以
can see sorry  alright so both ways this will be okay
写在免疫图上的免疫联合的大写
that the capitalization of the joint of immunity on the restive graph is written as
the product over all the nodes of the
写在免疫图上的免疫联合的大写
作为条件概率图所有节点上的乘积
graph of the conditional probabilities of X I excite the volume of you know the
的XI激发了你的力量，我知道除了暴力之外，这是一个
I given the violence apart this is an
amazing between position if you think about it right so you know in this case
的XI激发了你的力量，我知道除了暴力之外，这是一个
如果您考虑正确的话，位置之间会令人惊讶，所以您知道
amazing between position if you think about it right so you know in this case
在这种情况下，条件概率对应于它的no和this
the conditional probability corresponding to its no and this function is the condition of the
功能是给森林赋予效果的方式的条件。
way the effects are given its forests so mr. Bastian that factorization with this graph
巴斯蒂安（Bastian）通过此图分解因人而异的导弹
the personal missile dependent relation that we introduced which is certified ethical justification for deewana
我们介绍的关系是经过证明的道德正当理由
and discuss its Lewis okay so I
迪瓦娜（Deewana）并讨论它的刘易斯（Lewis）好吧，所以我将有确切的百年纪念的例子
will have exactly tricentennial examples and some a little bit more complicated but I'll ask
还有一些更复杂，但是我想请您认识夫人。布莱恩和
you to know mrs. Blaine and
electric artworks and washing us if we  can prove it
还有一些更复杂，但是我想请您认识夫人。布莱恩和
电子艺术品，如果我们能证明的话，就洗我们
electric artworks and washing us if we  can prove it
[音乐]
[Music]
上升和这些因素在这里这些功能是
Rises and this factors here these functions are the condition for committees of X i
当我们从
given sparks when we have this complicated factorization from the product rule well we only
产品规则很好，我们只有教过定居者的父母，
have the parents we have taught the settlers and the co parents and the novice
共同父母和新手，其他一切都来了，但是
and everything else is coming here but because of this independent relationship the the only
由于这种独立的关系，这里X i的唯一分区
partition here this X i given the parents of
给...的父母
所以我真的很确定自己在做什么我正在用身体做定向图
so I'm actually so sure what I'm doing I am taking a directed graph with
my body moves the first equation writes the the product rule so no independence assumptions
所以我真的很确定自己在做什么我正在用身体做定向图
移动第一个方程写乘积规则，所以没有独立性
my body moves the first equation writes the the product rule so no independence assumptions
假设我很爱，什么也没做，然后我就用这种方法
I am love assuming nothing and then I am applying sort of this equation right
等式对，我正在应用这个表示业务的等式
I'm applying this equation that says that business innovation is factorized this way and another
创新是通过这种方式进行分解的，而在这一方面则占主导地位
thing at this the predominate affects one because it's one has no parents all right
影响一个，因为它是一个没有父母可以防止的影响
the prevent effects still given x1 that's the only part I could still get enough
仍然给定x1，这是我唯一仍然可以获得足够的部分x1 x4
only x1 x4 given 2 and 3 and X 5 given 3 so remember you
2和3以及X 5给定3，所以请记住，您可以看到外观关系
can see the appearance relations that
有效地表示是否概率等于零，这意味着水平
effectively whether says the probability is equal to naught which means the level x3 expires
in the penitent water I mean
有效地表示是否概率等于零，这意味着水平
x3在pen悔水中过期，我的意思是看这2个方程式
looking at this 2 equation there never expiry x5 is independent off that's 124 right
到期时间x5是独立的，即124对
there it's here given x2 x3 x4 is
在这里给定x2 x3 x4独立于X 1给定X 1 X 3 in
independent of X 1 given X 1 X 3 in terms of X 2 etc
you may say I know but
在这里给定x2 x3 x4独立于X 1给定X 1 X 3 in
X 2等的术语，您可能会说我知道，但是我怎么知道这种独立关系
how do I know this independence relation  well we will spend a lecture or two and  we will
好吧，我们将花费一两次演讲，我们将
案件
cases
没关系，如果我们知道剩余权力的父母人数是多少
it's okay you know this if let's say is the number of parents to the
power left to describe this times times
没关系，如果我们知道剩余权力的父母人数是多少
描述这个时代
power left to describe this times times
原则上，实际上有人可以说夺权加一
in principle actually somebody can say take the power a plus one
你坐起来，但你知道这就像你对归一化感到满意，
you sit up but you know it's like if you're comfortable a normalization and everything
一切都差不多，这就是酒的帮助。
so that's approximately of the order wine is take aid to affect
反向对，这些将取一个值，而我们全取K个值
reverse right these are going to take a values and we're taking K values all  right so okay less rough
对，所以没那么粗糙
是的，新西兰对敌人的纪念较少，被驳回
yes NZ's enemy remembrances lesser dismissed mara independence relations okay and this is not very
玛拉独立关系还可以，这不是很有趣，所以这是
interesting so this is something very just the Ascension this you can appreciate the necessary
只是提升的东西，你可以体会到我所需要的
I'm showing that this function is a  probability right because you say 116  points along that mystical did you okay
表示此函数是概率正确的，因为您说116
沿着那个神秘的观点，你还好吗
I'm showing that this function is a  probability right because you say 116  points along that mystical did you okay
分布还可以，下一个经历等于一个很好的分布
the distributions okay next one to experience equal to one which is nice so obviously
因此，很明显，将标准化归因于个别情况 ，显然，这里的组成可以证明
it's individual on normalizing expect that this will be the case and apparently this the
composition here you can show that the national experience is actually it comes home service
因此，很明显，将标准化归因于个别情况 ，显然，这里的组成可以证明
体验是真的，家庭服务功能真的是
functions is really the conditional distribution which is what I tell you you need to
有条件的分配，这就是我告诉你的，你需要记住
remember okay this functions are very more general and they don't even have to be
函数是非常通用的，如果这样的话，它们甚至不一定是更好的选择
preferable if this but right now from directed graphs this is the case and I
但是现在从有向图来看就是这种情况，我说证明
say the proof and it works on extremely busy slide all right that's why I
可以在非常忙碌的幻灯片上正常工作，这就是为什么我要您键入您的
want you to type your homework because this rule was the lazy person typing the
作业，因为这条规则是懒惰的人打字幻灯片我的秘书
slide my secretary the novelist which imaginary person alright so it was me okay because
小说家，那个虚构的人还好，所以我还可以，因为我做不到
I can't imagine asking anybody that I've destroyed so it was this I want you
想象问一个人我被摧毁了，所以这就是我要你
to to need some type and by typing fails so
需要某种类型，并且通过键入失败，所以
那是因为您将需要进行此操作以进行特定的作业分配
that because you will need to do this for specific distribution your homework to do
things like that so the first part
那是因为您将需要进行此操作以进行特定的作业分配
做这样的事情，所以定理的第一部分是方法和响应
of the theorem was methods and responses  individually
个别地
[音乐]
[Music]
无线的秘密是可以进行某种计算的信号之一
the secrets wirelessly was one of the signals along okay sort of calculation that is
going to make the relations of
无线的秘密是可以进行某种计算的信号之一
这将使所有这些人的文章之间的关系变得极端
the article of all those extremely efficient okay define in terms of the notes and
可以根据笔记和父母的价值观进行有效的确定
the values of the parents minds within the operations rather in this case the marginalization
行动中的思想，而不是在这种情况下，边缘化是局部的
is a local operation right and this allows us to to  see immediately the distance
操作正确，这使我们能够立即看到距离
是他的密歇根州正常归化先生。正如我所说的
it's his Michigan the normalized properly okay okay mr. as I say those any functions
像这样的任何功能都可以使永久性区域分布很好
like that take the permanent zone distribution well I'm going to show you know that
将会告诉您，这和我写的各种清单中的一些
this and some of the various I write lists as the joint effects k plus
联合效应k加1和质量k加1除以k加1的幂
1 and the quality k plus 1 divided by the powers of k plus 1
and then I I calculate the numerator
联合效应k加1和质量k加1除以k加1的幂
然后II使用适当的公式计算分子分母
denominator using the appropriate  marginalization of the composition of  the joint of a new distribution
新发行的联合的组成的边缘化
扩大，确保做任何事情
expansion sure whatever done
好吧好吧好吧，这是好先生。 Lucius好吧，因为那是积极的
okay okay okay so this is the okay mr. Lucius okay because that's positive wearing
dark shirt and whatever else on
好吧好吧好吧，这是好先生。 Lucius好吧，因为那是积极的
穿着深色衬衫，以及检察官身上的其他物品，所以让我们穿上这件衣服，
the proctors so let's take this one and  the partnership give you some k plus and
合伙关系给你k +
而且因为我必须法医知道如果L不创建k的导频
and because I have to forensic aware that if L doesn't create the pilots of
k plus 1 is inside before camp yesterday right so I don't have to worry
而且因为我必须法医知道如果L不创建k的导频
加号1昨天在营地之前就在里面，所以我不必担心
about the parent and mr. McCann needed to learn outside the estimation because I don't
父母和先生麦肯需要在估计之外学习，因为我不
samel XK plus one or departments and you
samel XK加上一个或多个部门，您会注意到从这里到那里
notice from here to there I have to sound and the professionals from 1 to
声音和从1到K的专业人员，除了校园部分
K except the parts of campus where  elements will be possible  explain right there without a freshwater
不用淡水就可以在那里解释元素
因为这是非常重要的事情，因为我在做
because this is something extremely important right because I'm doing I'm pushing the summations inside
将总和推入内部我有一个潜力是可以的
I have a context that the potentials are okay according to my induction argument they're
根据我的归纳论证，它们确实是有条件的
really the conditional distributions and then I have this summation of the other factors that
分布，然后我得到了其他因素的总和
have no clear benefit so if you do this and we move this on the
没有明显的好处，所以如果您这样做，我们将在当地将其转移给您
local what you have to summon XK plus 1 because there's no X 2 plus
召唤XK加1，因为没有X 2加1，所以整个转换
1 so this whole transformation constants numerator denominator D summation constants and this factorization by
常数分子分母D求和常数和
根据定义，因式分解为1，因为此函数已规范化，所以我
definition is 1 because this functions are normalized so what I get is this conditional
得到的是，此条件分布等于我的因子FK加1，因此您
distribution is equal to my factor FK plus 1 so as you
根据条件证明构成收入分配不是
compose in revenue distribution in terms of conditionals the proof is not shortened to contagious
缩短为传染性就像交通艾滋病
is like traffic AIDS ok actually most books the parties consider a logician there's no
好的，实际上，大多数书籍都被当事方认为是逻辑学家，没有证据
proof okay inaudible any questions on this thing's right if another story our interest is
好吧，听不清关于这个问题的任何疑问，如果另一个故事
我们的兴趣实际上是这些当地意识的分解，
really the decomposition in terms of these local conscious that their conditional the values of
他们的条件是出埃及记12的父母的出埃及记
exodus 12 given its parents the resumption topology will here the destructor fundamental to the
拓扑将在这里构成我们所做的事情的基础的析构函数
type of things we do this with directed graph and the part that we have
这与有向图以及我们不合逻辑或导数的部分
it illogical or derivative is decelerations and insulation don't imagine that they have to sound
减速和绝缘不需要想象它们必须发出x1的声音
x1 an actual appears in all of these  functions
实际出现在所有这些功能中
我本人，但拖拉机只在这里固定底部的孤岛
myself but the tractor fixed islands only on the bottom here exclusively there right so
在那里，所以显然在这个问题上，您可以开始一些您提供的
obviously in this problems you can start some you provide to the left all right
左边到右边，如果示例如您所见，
and if examples as you see this so
that's important and then you'll notice you have some operations to put rods and notes
左边到右边，如果示例如您所见，
这很重要，然后您会注意到您进行了一些操作来放置杆和
where we sum up although the rest
记下我们在哪里总结，尽管身体的其余部分大部分都集中在
of the body most this is so focused on the operation we we have to
我们必须对玻璃进行的操作，其中模型左侧会强调
do with a glass with left of model stressing the context of why not kids
为什么孩子不喜欢与众不同的背景
like the different there is a problem to the complex all right I'm I always
复杂好吧，我总是喜欢正常的反面
like the opposite of the normal
case right I remember you know I said maybe this joke some time ago I
复杂好吧，我总是喜欢正常的反面
正确的案例我记得你知道我说过这个笑话
was trying to give a whole action on some topic and some people ask me
试图对某个话题采取整体行动，有人问我可以吗
can you start to give an example and I have not been introduced what the
开始举一个例子，而我还没有介绍这个主题是什么
topic was okay you know she'll never leave my case alive to give you the
好吧，你知道她永远不会离开我的案子，给你一段时间
period when the examples come later on he do the examples on your own so
例子来了，稍后他自己做例子，所以是的
yes sort of the people in one day so extra depends on X 1 X
一天之内的人，所以额外取决于X 1 X 2 X 2等，这样您就可以看到我说可以了
2 X 2 etc so you can see I say okay
of the write this as a product of the functions but intellectual inspires this is
一天之内的人，所以额外取决于X 1 X 2 X 2等，这样您就可以看到我说可以了
将此作为功能的产物，但知识分子对此有所启发
of the write this as a product of the functions but intellectual inspires this is
那么，益百利（Experian）明年将成为合作伙伴物理学的奇迹，而
nothing then experian the partner physics wonder next year and the pharmacist our experience it's
药剂师我们的经验是在接下来的三个，所以其他的你可以
for the next three so the other ones you can show you at least the
至少向您展示服务功能，它们什么都不是，或者
service functions they are nothing else or the the function of P of X clinics
X诊所的P的功能仍然是当x3的条件给定x2和
still is when the condition of x3 given x2 and I think mr. composition right
我想先生。构图权和II，您必须先了解该国
and I I you know the country first I have to calculate the joint if
计算如果X到XT除以T FX的联合，那么另一件事我
X to X T divided by T FX still so then the other thing I
have to some obviously to marginalize
计算如果X到XT除以T FX的联合，那么另一件事我
必须明显地将所有X 1 X 2 X 4或X 1和X 4边缘化
it's all X 1 X 2 X 4 or X 1 and X 4 and
you can see some of the things we'll
必须明显地将所有X 1 X 2 X 4或X 1和X 4边缘化
您可以看到我们将组织的一些事情可以看到很远的距离
organization can see long distance inside the trial and these parenthesis and visible practice comes
在试验中，这些括号和可见的实践来不及
too long to learn good idea to is f 3 or X 3 and X
学习好主意是f 3还是X 3和X 3就像是湍流完成
3 just is like a turbulent completed version of the theorem okay the best possible
定理的版本还可以吧，最好的函数吧
functions right and this conscience turn out to be pro communities is only for directed
而这种良心证明是专业社区，仅适用于有向图
graphs we said anything for undirected graphs the case to be very well general management
我们说了无向图的话，一般情况下都很好
理智管理至少可以在此马尔可夫语境中定位
of sanity can position at least in the context of this Markov chain about adoption
关于采用的链条功能更强大，所以这是一个例子
being a bit more powerful so this is an example from one of the textbook
机器学习中教科书的内容相似，因此其中一项便是
similar in machine learning so one of the notes is the glass is left one
玻璃是左边的知识之一就是可以在左边的支撑
of the knowledge is the support which can be on the left the other one
is a know that is raining
玻璃是左边的知识之一就是可以在左边的支撑
另一个是知道可能正在下雨的知识
which can be on earth and everyone is that it's cloudy I am a strong
而且每个人都在多云，我基本上是个坚强的依赖者
basically the dependencies look like the hot all right and let's follow the fuel that
看起来好像很热，让我们跟随我描述的
I described the junket ability of drama straight away the grass right is basically returnest
戏剧表演的中介能力基本回归
同时第一次甚至看到我们被原谅看到了什么
same time first even see we're forgiven see what not really given us an hour
并没有真正给我们一个小时，通过比较您可以看到的所有内容
and everything you can see by comparing this with examining the composition using the product
通过使用产品社区共享来检查组成是暗含的
community to share is implies basically fundamental national independence relations right and as a measure
基本上是基本的民族独立关系权
of the elections okay right that
衡量选举的方式还可以，您可以期待这一点
you can this you can expect this independence relations all right and then from this
好的独立关系，然后您可以说哦，这就是为什么
you can say oh that's why
the composition I mean in Pascal the new activist problem and you have this graph
好的独立关系，然后您可以说哦，这就是为什么
我在Pascal中指的是新的维权主义者问题的构成，你有这张图
like that smells you already have a
那样的气味你已经在图形独立性上有负面影响了
negative in the graphics independence relations so this decomposition is automatic you don't have to
关系，所以这种分解是自动的，您不必清除
clear anything right so we are going to define this distribution so effectively the trial
任何正确的方法，因此我们将非常有效地定义此分布，
审判价值很好，因为有一个组织来定义，这是从他的
value well because of an organization to define this is from his first loudest row
so if I do he wanted
审判价值很好，因为有一个组织来定义，这是从他的
第一个最大的行，所以如果我愿意的话，只要另一行是
as long as the other one is one line is nervously than one value let's
比一个值更令人担忧的是，这是镜面反射的概率
say this is the probability of the specular the hell are they so I am
他们到底是不是所以我正在写云很有可能是虚假的
writing is probability well the cloud is a false argument or a tool to describe
参数或工具来很好地描述这一点，实际上我没有
this well actually I have no
money from this I have to fill this I have different Lee's and if I
参数或工具来很好地描述这一点，实际上我没有
从这个钱我必须填补这个我有不同的李的，如果我把这个
take this little mini be how isn't it okay we come from the normalization because
小迷你是怎么回事，我们来自标准化，因为很多
for a lot of skilled problem it doesn't make a sense to say - wah
熟练的问题，这没什么好说的-哇-哇
- wah yeah we can subtract - fish - a problem with million borrowers we
是的，我们可以减去-鱼-有数百万借款人的问题，我们将
差额好吧，所以不用打扰我花了卡
will make a difference okay so no bother so I spent the card for this
problem is the times to the
差额好吧，所以不用打扰我花了卡
对于这个问题是随身携带的次数是下面的分数
carry case the number of points below and this environment variables that's why you see
和这个环境变量，这就是为什么您在那里看到它的原因
it through there actually I don't know why I different from before before using were
其实我不知道为什么我和以前使用K之前有所不同
using K from the number of values that are available can take here I just
从可用值的数量可以在这里我只是一个
a for another opponent the game you guys are adult and vaccinated so you can
另一个对手，你们的游戏是成年的并且已经接种了疫苗，这样您就可以确定
figure out in which life what the context is right so so I don't have
在哪种生活中背景是正确的，所以我不必回去
to go back and change the story that's already there and I was sure that
改变已经存在的故事，我确定每个人都回应
everybody responds what this equation makes or let's the the correlation rate across today from
这个方程式是什么，或者让我们得出今天以来的相关率
directly ghost makes a little sense
直接鬼是有道理的，没有别的好吧
there was nothing else okay all right
所以这11个例子我想我可能要举个例子，因为
so this 11 example I think I'm gonna I may have to give this because there's
该示例中令人不愉快的依赖关系作为在
unpleasant dependence relations from this example as applications in the slides so this is prevalence
滑动，所以这是你的盛行，你知道在不久的某个时候来认识你
of you know to come you know sometime in the near part of a future
未来的一部分，所以有这样的变量，最好是
so there are such variables and best on with the discussion of in the composition
在构图中的讨论这是我正确的x1 x2给定的x1 x3
this is what I have right x1 x2 given x1 x3 given X 1 X
5 etc X tix given X 2 X 5
在构图中的讨论这是我正确的x1 x2给定的x1 x3
给定X 1 X 5等X给定X 2 X 5受保护的权利，你在此说
protected right and and you say in this example a nice graphical representation of the
在这种情况下，可以很好地以图表形式展示桌会
table society to this conditional distribution is corresponding to each tsunami so x1 it's a
分布与每个海啸相对应，因此x1是一个很长的经验
long experience given x1 so it's a baby like this exports given x2 table like
给定x1，所以它是一个像这样的婴儿，给定x2表，就这样存在
this exist given two values okay it's a table like that and like that I
给定两个值，好吧，这是一张像这样的桌子，我必须
have to actually program I'm assuming and I'm saying this that show the kid and
我假设的程序，我说的是向孩子展示并记下
take note and destroy that we assign you some homework problems when we don't do
当我们不做这个问题时，破坏我们为您分配一些家庭作业问题
the question all right you have something only  computer program to do this for you
好吧，您只有电脑程序才能为您执行此操作
不要吃这个不要吃这个已经做了这个安东尼高迪
don't eat this don't eat this already did this Antoni gaudí
好的，有一个时间陪他们，那怎么可能
okay guys there's a time for them how's that possible I don't have the power
我没有力量，你知道为什么他们的机器上没有一台非常好的机器
you know why not a very good machine ever left of their other thing you
你们离开我的另一件事，因为您永远都不会去几乎论文
guys left me because you'll never never go almost papers right that's the 30 minutes
对，那就是30分钟，好吧，让我们看一下必要放的东西，我要走了
all right let's see necessarily put so I'm going  to my past
到我的过去
好吧，那么哪个性别歧视者就可以了，那么这就是我们
and okay so which of the sexist is coming all right so then this is
our independent of each other and that's the concept of the latest Paris fire okay
好吧，那么哪个性别歧视者就可以了，那么这就是我们
彼此独立，这就是最新的巴黎大火的概念，所以 这是我的NRI，如果我不知道为什么他们是独立的，这是独立的
so so it's my NRI all right this are independent if I didn't know why
they're nervous values of X 1 and X 4 whatever I get they depend on
彼此独立，这就是最新的巴黎大火的概念，所以 这是我的NRI，如果我不知道为什么他们是独立的，这是独立的
X 1和X 4的神经值，无论我得到什么，它们都相互依赖，这是
each other this is sort of a song another problem will reduce you know in
像是一首歌另一个问题会减少你对各种事物的了解
in sort of mixed models but many other settings as well  okay
型号，但还有许多其他设置也可以
两件事-这个比利时误导高斯人是一两件事，所以如果我
two things - one and two long is this Belgium to mislead Gaussian so if
I wrote a little bit of white for it sex the this exercising defendant and
两件事-这个比利时误导高斯人是一两件事，所以如果我
为此运动被告写了一点白色
so effectively you know this is the problem engine roaring tons of the divinity of
实际上，您知道这是发动机呼啸而过的神性问题
the world X given Y and the lamented
给定Y的世界X和给与士兵性的哀叹的X生活
world X living who soldier sex is given Y can be factorized over the data
由于可以假设X为
right because of this assumption that the X is having a fairly given Y ok
有一个确定的Y ok，所以这是非常重要的
so so this is something very important laughter moment of birth under the name of
以朴素贝叶斯分类器的名义出生的笑声时刻，我的意思是我
naive Bayes classifier i mean i
satisfy a fear you know i know this but additionally basically has been this is
以朴素贝叶斯分类器的名义出生的笑声时刻，我的意思是我
满足一个恐惧，你知道我知道这一点，但另外基本上已经是
that that's fine to say become from now
可以这么说，从现在开始成为成千上万的人，这就是
someone and thousand through so that's what the name plus pi or take this complexed
加上pi是什么名字，或者说复杂一点，然后说各节是
and say the sections are linearly independent given y and you notice on this paragraph
线性独立给定y，如果您看到
if you see on the birthday all right I started fatal dependencies between the exes
生日好了，我开始之间的致命依赖
okay so this is the display the
exes好的，所以这是打印出来的我的Vegas被解雇的显示器
printed my Vegas was fired okay to come up with your own little algorithms and
用自己的小算法，如果您搜索文献，就可以
this if you search in the literature you
will find very particular algorithm it's for leveling this demented name they discussed fire okay
用自己的小算法，如果您搜索文献，就可以
会发现非常特殊的算法，用于平整这个痴呆的名字
will find very particular algorithm it's for leveling this demented name they discussed fire okay
讨论过火好吧，是的，我只知道您是否还记得那个名字地下室，
yes well I just know if you remember that name basements that these types of
这些类型的性爱运行正常且独立，所以您
sex running right and independent so you have a nice proposition that looks like this
有一个不错的建议，看起来像这样
okay and constants with dependencies between the extras and because the balance is still maintained
和常量之间有依赖关系的常量，因为余额是
仍然维持了一些您可以做的薪酬结构，但差额
some pay structure that you can do is the difference but the  custom what you see on the top okay
自定义您在顶部看到的内容，好吗
这是普遍存在的条件独立关系国防关系
it's prevalent conditional independence relations National Defense relations so these actions right so this is
这些动作没错，没关系，这是出场时间
all right this is the length of appearances this is referred directly best luck sir
直接被称为“祝你好运，先生，好，我们的党依存关系”
okay and the party dependencies we have this one we introduced the Vegas more longer
从现在开始，我们在大约两条腿上介绍了拉斯维加斯更长的时间，因此您可以
in about two legs from now so you can
work from something from collective one  connected personal between the first
从现在开始，我们在大约两条腿上介绍了拉斯维加斯更长的时间，因此您可以
从第一个人之间相互联系的集体中的某件事开始工作
work from something from collective one  connected personal between the first
好吧，那里没有新东西
okay there is nothing new there
但我是后代，甚至是父母，然后是后代，甚至是父母
but I am descendants even the parents then the descendants even the parents  and
和
接受事实有向图的基本性质不同
accept the fact the fundamental property of directed graphs the different position from the parable
寓言寓言中的位置再次说服您的敏感者
sprouts to convince your sensitive actually again the fulfilled never step two is this marginalization
从未实现的第二步是我们在第二步中所做的这种边缘化
that we did in two examples before and then you can treat  this decomposition is correct
之前的例子，然后您就可以认为这种分解是正确的
[音乐]
[Music]
一个极端
one extreme
x1 x2时代的专家，这种高效的外观没有错
experts in the time of x1 x2 and there's not wrong exterior to this efficient
正确的
right
-好的，多田听着，当你的生活很完美的时候
- okay listen tada your life is perfect when it's the expected by P of
X 1 is 50 ok by you
-好的，多田听着，当你的生活很完美的时候
X的P期望的X是50 ok alpha加X 1 X 2 X 3 X 4就是
alpha plus X 1 X 2 X 3 X 4 is that what happens to
X 5 and X 6 fear of insulin
X的P期望的X是50 ok alpha加X 1 X 2 X 3 X 4就是
X 5和X 6发生胰岛素恐惧X 5减去X 6发生了什么
what happened to X 5 minus X 6 well I mean the question of attack
好吧，我的意思是说，攻击的问题是黑人，当您
the black is words you know when you somewhere X 5 and X 6 this
在X 5和X 6处，这等于0.1等于1，所以它们消失了
is 0.1 of this equal to 1 so they disappear you see that when you
看到当您在接下来的5分钟内分析关节时，因为这
analyze to the joint the next 5 minutes because this how conditional distinguishes the summation
有条件的区分总和给人好处，所以所以这
is giving the advantage okay so so this
is the joint of X 1 X 2 X 3 X 4 and then if
有条件的区分总和给人好处，所以所以这
是X 1 X 2 X 3 X 4的关节，然后如果您想加入音高1 X 2 X
you wanted to join the pitch 1 X 2 X
3 we have to something that's clear but when someone experimenting disappearing because summation of
是X 1 X 2 X 3 X 4的关节，然后如果您想加入音高1 X 2 X
3我们必须清楚一些，但是当有人尝试消失时
3 we have to something that's clear but when someone experimenting disappearing because summation of
因为驱逐所有人的总和
expelling everyone all right yeah well this consus without this concept evolved already but you
是的，没有这个概念的这种疑惑已经发展了，但是你明白了
get this perfect score given X 2 okay so this is kinda filled this independence
给定X 2的完美分数，好吧，这有点满足了这种独立性关系
relation but I wrestle to remember the ideas that Assad isn't behind all of this
但是我努力地想起了阿萨德不在所有这些背后的想法，并说
and say all there is an independence relations but to heaven all the groups of
一切都有独立的关系，但到天堂的所有团体
this graph and he says this graph implies none of this independence relations so whatever
图，他说这个图不暗示这种独立关系
因此，无论人口分布图是tamarkan满足的，
distribution that population the graph has been tamarkan satisfy of this relationship okay a stupid
这种关系还不错，所以我们不会
idea so we're not going to
do the algebra but we lived  that vision server browser arguments  implants University what is relationship
这种关系还不错，所以我们不会
做代数，但我们过着视觉服务器浏览器参数
do the algebra but we lived  that vision server browser arguments  implants University what is relationship
植入大学是什么关系
这是巴黎关系X 1的结束，因为X 6是X的头
and here is an over in the Paris relation X 1 given X 6 is
the head of X 3 X 3 this is like in the in this case
这是巴黎关系X 1的结束，因为X 6是X的头
3 X 3这就像在这种疾病的情况下说癌症，为什么是
of disease that say cancer and why is
somehow kind of a disease you know some of molecule blood or other things so
3 X 3这就像在这种疾病的情况下说癌症，为什么是
您以某种方式知道某种分子血液或其他东西，因此为什么
why is the disease right but the memory access many diseases and you have something
是正确的疾病，但是记忆会访问许多疾病，而您有
that can be derived from any
可能来自任何疾病的东西，所以您可以看到一点点
diseases so you can see this as a little from X to Y so exist
从X到Y，所以存在另一件事-您可以看到这是意识问题
another thing the - you can see this is awareness problem that if you have
如果您有其他人，比如说验血，请询问成员
an alternate and let's say a blood test you ask the members area and so
this graph that you see in
如果您有其他人，比如说验血，请询问成员
区域，所以您在spitzer中看到的这张图讨论了您知道这不是
spitzer discuss you know this isn't about the narrative rondelle the joint affection Y as
关于叙事rondelle联合情感Y作为可能的效果
the probable effects knives the probability of Y given X so reliable addressed you know
刀给定X的概率给定Y如此可靠，您知道这一点，您
this you know the parent effects may be will  define it by
知道父母的影响可能是通过定义
对对对
right right okay
[音乐]
[Music]
从X到Y美味，但不允许您成为任何朋友res或
delicious from X to Y but that doesn't allow you can be any friends res
or something for y and say what desserts  okay
从X到Y美味，但不允许您成为任何朋友res或
y的东西，说什么甜点可以
or something for y and say what desserts  okay
他们提供了下两张幻灯片，我们将讨论和下雨
they delivered the next two slides we will discuss and rain
好吧好吧好吧，这是正确的
okay right okay so this is the right
[音乐]
[Music]
衣服是湿的，但让我知道你是否Dre
dress is wet but let me let you know whether Dre
[音乐]
[Music]
这已经说明草是湿的
this has already explained that the grass is wet okay we will formally serve this
好的，我们将以派生的形式正式提供此服务，但实际上，如果
with a derivation okay but in essence if this  example all right
好样的
也许今天没有问题
no problems maybe today
用小名字说，你有两点，学生在做那种
with little names let's say you have two points the students are doing the kind
of it thank you go gents you know come
用小名字说，你有两点，学生在做那种
谢谢你去，你知道得到的绅士不依赖任何东西，所以
to get doesn't depend on anything so they're putting the feather corns let's say this
他们放羽毛玉米，让我们说这个，这个对，所以让我们
and this right so let's Alchemist is right this is zero okay so this has
炼金术士是对的，这是零好，所以这是探索性的，所以他们是对的，所以
exploratory they so right so this is Center for the experiment a  phenomenal
这是一个惊人的实验中心
我在幻灯片中报告了这一点，您知道在游戏中输掉了比赛
I was reporting this in the slides you know losing the game in the factorization
我们想念的因式分解实际上可以计算出受众群体并进行
which we miss you can actually compute an audience and do the algebra nothing Ranger
代数没有游侠，所以这是我们开始的分解，因此您可以
so this is the factorization we started so you can actually prove all the questions
实际证明您在上一张幻灯片中看到的所有问题
that you saw in the previous slides
我与道格拉斯的关系，所以我只想说说事情变得容易些，所以请记住我们
my ass Douglas relation so let me just say what's going easier so remember we
sent that you know X of the royal
我与道格拉斯的关系，所以我只想说说事情变得容易些，所以请记住我们
发送您知道皇家后代的X好，所以基本上是董事会
descendants okay so basically the board is independent of anything else okay the SAT score
与SAT分数或正在清除的速率无关
or what rate is clearing out
that cetera  question on the doctor okay it says
与SAT分数或正在清除的速率无关
医生的那个老问题，好吧，它说
that cetera  question on the doctor okay it says
准社交给了他们考试的难度
parasocial was given them the difficulty of an exam all right it's also kind of
这也是一种地狱，好吧，这不是我写的
hell okay that's not what I wrote it
然而，有关他的后代的信息说
however informational says about its descendants
好久了，我只想让句子不要用等式呼吸
well so long I just want the sentence against not breathing with an equation any
关于后代的任何信息都包含有关本发明的信念
information about the descendants contains beliefs about this invention reasoning process so another race if
推理过程，所以如果您知道发生了什么，那又是一场比赛
you know what happened was still there it has got there okay it changes the
到那里好了，即使是谁，它也可以改变画面
picture okay even who says the difficulty on the intelligence of the Skinner right if
说如果证据是Skinner的智力上的困难
the evidence is the difficulty of in Excel and even peasants sugar still smells but
在Excel中的困难，甚至农民糖仍然闻起来，但
the official from below the most immortality do the fixer okay so we will see
从下面的永生不朽的官员做固定器好吧，所以我们会看到这个
this sort of problem when we discuss  independence relationships and and  evidence okay
我们讨论独立性关系时会遇到一些问题，并且
证据还可以
this sort of problem when we discuss  independence relationships and and  evidence okay
[音乐]
[Music]
好的
okay
[音乐]
[Music]
这就是增长，徽标就是这个使命的形象
and this would be the growth and the logo is this image on just the
mission we have sent up over all the she's invaluable success okay so then this
这就是增长，徽标就是这个使命的形象
我们已经把所有她宝贵的成功都派上了用场，所以接下来
have the visceral volume is the Sabbath
内脏的体积是安息日甚至是vartanus，这有点
even vartanus and this is sort of the main cost that allows you develop native
我现在唯一能做的就是让您开发本机环境的主要成本
environments now the only thing I was
gonna say is a little socially desirable but Sir I was seven gardeners there was
我现在唯一能做的就是让您开发本机环境的主要成本
会说在社会上有点可取，但先生，我是七个园丁
the number of mobile growth so
移动设备的数量有增长，所以我们可以考虑一个渐进式的发展方式
we can think of a gradual and that way the death of our decisions coming
我们决定的死亡即将到来，因此杀手级病毒可能成为指示
so the killer virus can be maybe indicator punch values that tells you what it's
打孔值告诉你什么是美丽的收集-什么
beautiful collect - what Gaussian envelopes are they too late or what you know okay
高斯信封是不是为时已晚或您知道吗，所以生活就是
so life is the composition is right that this hidden garden was the morning with
构图是正确的，这个隐藏的花园是早晨，
a number of the additional volume which in the graph  you can keep the prosperous
在图表中可以保持繁荣的额外数量
服务参数theta是独立的，但与您收集的数据无关
service parameters theta are independent but independent of the data you collect in the problem
在这个问题中，可以肯定的是，在这里真正的问题
okay sure and in real problems here in the formation of the rebels will go
叛军的形成将能够实现，这证明了这一点。
to be able to achieve is a testament to this  data parameters theta but this bottom of
数据参数theta但该值的底部
任务要仔细考虑各种因素，并以某种方式必须实例化
missions to carefully account for the factors and somehow instance you have to do predictions
通过学生的信息来做预测，以了解在这几个人中没有人
by information of the students to know is nobody here in a few weeks from
now but because not wait a
通过学生的信息来做预测，以了解在这几个人中没有人
从现在起的几周内，但因为不等一分钟，非常自然的自我
minute and the very natural self directly linked to my website at least the previous
直接链接到我的网站，至少是上一个，而且这个网站已经很好 知道，下周二我会在这里看到
one and this nice already aware and I will see here on next  Tuesday suppose